[music]
>> Yo, what's good, guys? It's your girl
Sia, aka peach sprinkles. And welcome
back to another video, baby. If you're
new to the channel or you see my face
for the first time, please don't forget
to hit the subscribe button and the
notification bell to notify you next
time [bell] a video drops on this
channel. If you're returning, sorry.
Welcome. Your favorite show is on.
No context yet. I just want to make
lunch and I just thought I should vlog
cuz I wanted to show you guys like a
life hack.
So,
I ordered chicken from Pick 'n Pay.
It's chicken wings and some sweet corn
rice.
So, this is 1.5 kg 1.5 kg chicken wings.
So, what I usually do is cuz I stay
alone, right? And I get these like full
meals. Sometimes like pap and chakalaka
and morogo and what what and what what.
I just make quick meals. Oh, also, this
came out as this for people that don't
have a huge appetite. So, if you don't
mind eating like two sweet corns and
some wings for lunch, [music]
then
stick around. It's basically grilled
dinner or lunch, whatever. But,
>> [music]
>> yeah.
Oh.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, I understand what they mean now.
It's Sorry, I have to oppose. Okay, so
first things first, you're going to want
to wash [snorts]
your chicken
chicken wings
with the kitchen scissors.
Cut, cut, cut.
And then I don't usually measure how
much I cook. I just estimate what's
going to be enough for me to eat now and
eat later. Like I basically cook so that
I have leftovers for at least one more
time. So,
um I should have like four chicken wings
and two sweet corn for lunch. So, I can
make eight wings so that I can have
>> [music]
>> some of it for dinner, but my friend is
also coming over, so I'm probably going
to make 12.
Yeah.
That sounds like a lot, but trust.
This is how big the wings are for
reference, so four is more than enough
also.
6,
8, 9 ish. Yeah, that looks like a lot. I
think this is enough.
I actually think Also, she doesn't eat a
lot, so
yeah, we [music] good. Let me wash this
quickly and then I'll show you the next
step.
Okay, so in this bowl we have our
chicken freshly washed. I first start
with some olive
oil and just
sprinkle a little bit of that, not too
much.
And then
This is the secret ingredient.
This is the life hack.
So, in one compartment you have the
cooking bag and then in the other you
have the actual like seasoning, like the
marinade. So, you basically season your
chicken with the spice.
Make sure it's well coated all around,
neh?
And then
And then with the bag that it comes
with, this is your chicken all coated.
With the bag that it comes in, this is
where we're going to cook our chicken in
the oven. So, I usually use the oven and
it cooks
so good. Like, the chicken literally
falls off the bone when you're eating it
and then it's so tasty like this. The
spice is so good. It's sticky chicken
wings. I know there's also barbecue
flavor. I love the sticky chicken,
especially when I'm generally just
craving like barbecue chicken um sticky
barbecue basted wings or whatever. I
usually do that and then I'll just add
like a bit of peri-peri to make it like
a bit spicy. Usually, this is not um
enough for me.
I go in with some Worcestershire sauce.
I don't know if it's Worcestershire or
Worcestershire, whatever it's called.
But, I go in with the sauce, not a lot.
Just enough to give it some flavor. Just
in case
And then, I add the sweet and sticky
marinade, but like a spoon and a half
almost.
I don't add like a lot.
And then I go in with a little bit of
the steakhouse sauce, as well.
Two more ingredients, I'm almost done.
These are two of the most important
ingredients in this recipe.
Some bay leaves.
And then I also add some rosemary. You
can never go wrong with a good rosemary.
I promise you. This is what it looks
like. It tastes so good. This will give
your food so much aroma, like trust me.
I add just one of that. Sometimes I go
ahead and then I look for like one
that's small. Let me cut this in half
cuz other side is bad. Then I'm going to
go in with some garlic powder, onion
powder, ground cumin, and black pepper.
I know I said two more, but this is the
last four. All done.
When you're done, your chicken should
look something like this, and then you
mix mix mix. Put it in this oven bag.
Seal it. It comes with something to
actually like um seal it. It looks like
a zip lock. And then you put it in the
oven at 180° and let that cook till it's
fully done. I promise you the chicken
comes out so good every time. I might
actually just um pick up the camera
again when my friend lands, so she does
like a taste test for you guys, like a
review. So, you guys could understand
how good this thing tastes. Like, I
promise you, bruh. And then in a
separate pot, I'm going to cook my um
sweet corn, and that's what I'm going to
have the wings with. So, it's two for
me, two for her. And yeah, I'll talk to
you guys when I'm done cooking so I can
show you guys the finished results.
>> 2 hours later.
>> I know I said I was going to show you
the finished product, but
We're done eating.
>> Guys know we done the food. Oh my god.
>> Appreciate you. Come, let's go.
>> Uh-huh.
>> I'll talk to you guys soon. I'm thirsty.
I actually think I'm going to pass by
the garage.
I'll talk to you guys
later or tomorrow. Bye.
Ooh, that's so good.
Mmm, eat all of it.
Baby.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey my souls, I'm back from the hair
salon. I got my hair done. So, I went
for a half up, half down. It's been the
whole day cuz when I went to the salon,
I know it was in the morning at around
like 11-ish and now it's like now I'm
8:00 [music] p.m.
Yeah, it's like quarter to 9:00 p.m. So,
it's been the whole day. So, it's a bit
frizzy, but I'll I'll flat iron it again
and
refresh it tomorrow because I want to do
my makeup and shoot some content
outside. Anyways, I got some flowers.
I got some flowers. I just tried to
arrange them now. I didn't do a great
job, but this note Can I read what he
said? So, this is a note that the
flowers came with and the note says, "I
saw that your flower vase was empty.
Where's your boyfriend?
Let me fill that up for you." He is such
a flirt.
Anyways, you are They are really pretty
and I feel like they genuinely
compliment my [music] space.
Anyways, I'm going to clean up my house.
I have to sweep, wash the dishes, mop.
It's a mess. I'll take you guys along,
but I just leave the camera rolling
while I'm washing the dishes. Do you
guys want to see that? I don't know.
>> [music]
[music]
[music and singing]
>> You can't even sit in peace. [music]
Cuz all of these [\h__\h] be on you.
>> [music]
>> I'm just saying I can be
Yeah, [music]
fun that you call and you talk to a
girl.
I'll share my world [music] with you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> You could have all the
>> [music]
>> space.
All that you need.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Ain't no more pressure here. We ain't
got time
to
waste.
Wasting time.
>> [music]
>> And I ain't worried about them.
Girl, you wanted I see.
And I [music] am for real.
And I'll be where I be.
If you ever hit me on a late night.
I'll [music] give you a piece of my
mind.
Might give you some insight. I'll share
my world with you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> You [music] could have all the
>> [singing]
>> space.
All that you need.
>> [singing]
[music]
>> Ain't no more pressure here. We ain't
got time
to waste.
>> [music]
>> Wasting time.
Close your eyes [music] to get away.
Bang my line if I'm a friend.
Beautiful [singing]
girl, you staying this. You'll be fine.
I'll be [music] back.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey my dolls, welcome back to another
day in the vlog. Would you guys like me
to start speaking normally? Like talk
with a z, like say, welcome back, how
you doing? Do you guys want me to stop
doing that or do you want me to
Actually, why am I even asking for
permission? Anyways, today I want to use
the mic. I realized that I get too
comfortable with the audio of my camera
in its natural
form without adding any external
microphone. So, for research purposes,
I'm going to be using my mic. Hold on,
girl. Bear with me.
All right, I think it's really bad for
you. I think it's really Okay, cool. So,
I have an unboxing first things first. I
got
Okay.
So, guys, I just want to say like I want
to make it known in case you guys don't
already know, I am a victim of
e-ads, e-advertising. You see how you
feel like influencers promote products,
they do this, people buy products,
whatever, whatever.
I am dealer type, I'm not the one that
always goes and buys whatever is being
>> [laughter]
>> advertised because I want to try it for
myself. If you're saying this thing is
too good to be true and if you want to
buy one, I want to see.
So, and by God's grace, thankfully, we
do have e-money sometimes to spend on
those things. So, this is how we got
this package today. I was scrolling on
Instagram, I saw an ad on some
niacinamide body wash that apparently
helps get rid of your body acne. It
helps even out your skin tone,
especially your hands. I do have a lot
of hyperpigmentation across my body. So,
when that lady was just talking about
how it helped that lightened her stretch
marks, it did this, it did that, I'm
like,
okay.
This is the thing, and it better do what
you claim it does.
If it's a scissor,
so that we can open the box together. I
got like a full-on
um combo.
So, instead of buying the body wash or
the cream alone, I bought the whole
thing. So, it's the cream, it's the oil,
and the body wash, all from the same
range, of course. Just to also increase
the chances of it being effective, you
know?
Okay. So, in the box, this is
These are the products.
Mhm, I'm kind of excited for this.
I love Indonesian skin care products or
makeup.
Love it, though.
Oh, the packaging is beautiful.
Okay, so this is the pastry body wash.
This is the glycolic acid pomegranate
fragrance body wash, and then we have
the body lotion. This has niacinamide
and grapefruit extracts, and then we
have the
body oil.
This is a brightening body oil. I got
this as a combo for my body care
routine. I'm going to leave this in the
shower, and then every day I am going to
be using this body lotion and the oil
right after to,
you [snorts] know, maximize results. I
want to make sure that I use it
correctly. So, yeah, I'm pretty excited.
Usually, I give like these things like a
month, a month and a half to kind of
compare results. So, I'll be using this
until the end of August. If it lasts me
till the end of August, that is. And
then I'll give you guys an update the
same way that I did with the
the Mizani hair serum.
We also [snorts] passed by Clicks.
I got some cotton. Um in the cotton in
the cotton so I I got some cotton pads.
I got a face cloth because I don't know.
I change my face cloth every
2 months.
So, sometimes every month depending on
how I feel. I also got these detangling
combs from SoBae at Clicks because I'm
going to be wearing out my natural hair
tomorrow. Oh, we're going to the salon.
I'll I'll tell you guys all about that.
I got some Native Child for in the exam.
And then I also got the shampoo. This is
sulfate-free. This is vegan and it's
also paraben-free. So, it doesn't really
dry out your natural hair when you wash
your hair. You know how sometimes you
wash your natural hair and then it feels
like e
it hurts gray hair like it clean and
easy to bench. So, this does not do
that. It cleanses your hair like from
the scalp all the way to the end. But it
doesn't dry out your hair. So, I really
love this Native Child one. This is also
not promo. And I usually follow in with
the the milk and honey moisture cream.
I got lens wipes to wipe my prescription
glasses cuz sometimes I don't have I'm
not wearing the right material to use my
um shirt to like clean my glasses. So, I
just got this. I feel like they'd be so
handy to leave in the car. Also to like
wipe my car screen.
Also got [snorts] this Native Child with
shea butter moisturizing whatever. So,
this is in a sachet meaning that it it's
it's only going to be for one-time use.
I'm going to undo my hair tomorrow like
I said and wash my natural hair. This is
what I'm going to moisturize it with and
then follow in with this. I got a grape
sizer. I got some hair elastic bands.
>> [snorts]
>> And then I I some hand lotion from
Nivea. I got this eucalyptus oil to
steam cuz sometimes I have like
sinuses and I feel mucus in my throat
and whatever. So sometimes when I just
want to open up and relieve my breathing
a bit more, I use eucalyptus oil and
just like cover myself with a towel and
just steam
for however long and I find that my
breathing is so much better after that.
I got some gum for a cough.
I don't know. Someone said that instead
of using the internet fluoride
toothpaste or whitening toothpaste, just
use hydrogen peroxide to
gargle.
to
What's this called?
gargle Because I have braces, it's so
easy for me to get like stains on my
teeth, especially when I eat food that
has like curry, like staining food
basically that
leaves my teeth a bit It's either it
leaves my teeth a bit yellowish before I
brush my teeth or I have a discoloration
on my elastics. That's how I usually
know that the food that I ate
Yeah. So I went on Tik Tok naturally and
I tried to find like DIY
home remedies whatever besides like the
whitening toothpaste and the whatever
and I saw this. Someone was like do this
but do it in moderate amounts and don't
do it every day because it's very very
strong. This can also be used as a
bleach and but then the apparently
people also add this to their creams and
whatever for a hyperpigmentation and
don't do any There's a lot of uses but
what I do know, what I've collected is
that
This girl is dangerous. This girl is not
to be played with. So, tell I'm serious
now, you better be You must know what
you're doing.
So,
yeah, I'm going to
try it out.
But, not today, of course. That's it.
So, today I basically just was running
my errands. I wanted to shoot a video
for Fashion Never, but I finished
getting ready so late, and it felt like
by the time I drove there, finished my
brother, and then started setting up and
started shooting, it was going to be so
dark, and I'm All I wanted to do
honestly do like outdoorsy content
today, so I'll probably just do that
tomorrow. Tomorrow we're going to go to
Field Creations to do my hair. I'm going
to unbraid my cornrows under this wig.
I'm going to remove my wig, unbraid my
cornrows, wash my hair, and moisturize
it overnight with the products that I
got. And then tomorrow morning we're
going to wake up, go to the salon, and
get our hair nice and braided. I'm
thinking of getting Jada Weada braids,
and then I'm going to use those curling
bundles that I got from Fairytopia in
the last last last vlog. You guys
remember that? I'm going to use those
same bundles for tomorrow's hairstyle.
Basically Basically reusing the bundles.
Multi-purpose. Give me the number.
>> [laughter]
>> So, yeah, that's it for today. I think
Anyways, I want to go
>> [snorts]
>> I want to go cuddle. I want to be meat
cuddled, and I'm not doing anything else
today. I don't have any deadlines.
So, I think it's safe to say Uber.
I'm doing car hire and you want to find
a mercy. When I posted the notes from
the flowers that Umpana gave me, he saw
my nails. He's like, "Ew, what are
those?" And then I forgot my nails to go
get my nails done. So, we're also going
to We're also going to be getting my
nails done tomorrow. So, I'm doing my
hair. I'm going to take my baby sister
to her orthodontist, a new orthodontist.
I'm going to a with my friend Amanda. It
was her recommendation to take my sister
to that orthodontist.
And then, probably going to pass by and
get ice cream, and then
I'm going to go for my nail appointment.
Might do my lashes. I don't know. But,
yeah, guys, stay tuned for that. In the
meantime,
I'm going to go tomorrow morning.
Oh, hi, Kay. I was about to vent to you
guys about how much Cilesha kind of
appointment, but we have finally
>> [laughter]
>> We've finally found a place. I got my
hands done today.
Out. Khanyile no late for Khanyile.
We are so lost.
Oh, we are so lost.
No, no, I know. It's supposed to be two.
It's two.
Okay, let's use the lift.
But, we can walk for our steps,
Khanyile.
Okay, Nono, try. Every channel, I can't
WALK FOR STEPS.
BUT, AMANDA, DON'T YOU HAVE YOUR APPLE
WATCH? We can walk for steps. Tell me I
don't have to close rings, you know.
I I don't have to close earrings, you
know.
>> [laughter]
>> But, we can walk for steps.
People, like, before I start vlogging,
can I please get consent? Do you guys
consent to me vlogging?
Yes.
>> Yes, you're bringing more customers,
okay?
>> Okay, I have consent to vlog. Amanda.
>> This is my favorite place in the whole
world.
>> [laughter]
>> Hi.
>> Um, yes, I'm going to sit.
>> Yeah.
>> To those that goes, I was not back.
>> Khanyile, look at the lashes.
Russian.
>> Oh, inner trauma.
>> [laughter]
>> Chimmy, I love this.
Khanyile, too, now I can't
>> [laughter]
>> This should be your intro. I come back.
Did you guys miss me? Cuz I did miss
miss y'all. Anyway guys, welcome back to
my YouTube channel. My name is Amanda
and don't forget to like, subscribe,
tell your friends, tell their friends,
tell their friends.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay guys, I'm back. I'm better. I've
lost weight. What else? Oh, I got
braces. Sia has more new friends as
usual.
>> [laughter]
>> Amanda was like to me, "If you ever get
new friends, I'm cutting you off."
And she like he did, but she was very
subtle with that. She was like, "I'm
just going to keep my distance
since you got new friends, since you got
your degree."
>> I need you to have a YouTube channel,
like
Guys,
so Amanda Amanda happens to be Sia's
other sister. I'm the big sister.
So
>> [laughter]
>> This is This is I know you're probably
watching this and you're so mad, but
>> [laughter]
>> No, I I told her I was going to do this
when I see you on the YouTube. So I
you're so predictable.
But anyway,
So guys, we're fixing our braces. If you
want to do your braces,
this place is the place. Very affordable
and doesn't really break the budget, but
>> Yeah.
You told me I want this camera. Yeah,
yeah.
>> fresh
Then I'm going to take the camera.
>> No,
no, I'm saying like in the zoom.
When I see it, you know, I'm going to
take the camera to vlog.
And leave the camera in the house so
that every time she sees the camera, she
has motivation to vlog. Girl mess.
Girl mess.
>> I mean, he did it.
>> Like girl mess.
What if I buy the camera first? When I
see the camera everyday, I'll have
motivation to vlog from here.
But anyways, you guys my baby sister
Amanda is getting her braces at this
place. This is her first time here.
I don't want to show her face cuz it's
she's a baby and she's in school uniform
and you know how weird things are on the
internet with girl children these days.
So, I don't want to show my baby sister
on the internet, but
she's getting her braces now. And then
after here, I'm going to drop her off
back at home and then Amanda and I are
going to go find a nice place to get
matcha if they're still open, fingers
crossed because going back to Joburg, we
know that there's going to be traffic.
So, I hopefully we don't get stuck in
traffic to the point that now Kumyama go
by leeway.
And we can't even get like kid stuff.
But she left and left she left.
Guys, I want to mention actually, my
sister used to get her braces done at
Sandton Dentistry. So, apparently they
moved, but then the new address is not
communicated and my mom's been trying to
call to find out, "But where did you
guys move to cuz my child has the
appointment 2 months ago."
There's no response. So, we decided,
"You know what? Let's just find another
practice so that she continues with the
braces like it cuz her braces journey is
not going to work just because the
clinic vanished. Like they literally got
up and left.
Okay, cool. Zafika, I don't know what to
tell you. You're going to need to find
that clinic and come with the file cuz
we can't do anything
on her until we get a consent from your
previous orthodontist. Otherwise, they
can sue us.
So, that's what we're trying to like
figure out now, but they're finally
getting started on her. For now, at
least it's just like the cleaning. They
did x-rays.
I don't know if you can hear me over
this, but they did x-rays. They can make
They did the x-rays and then after the
x-rays, now they're just doing like the
cleaning
and then
uh fingers crossed
she can come start coming with Amanda
for
the appointment. Amanda is basically
going to babysit.
Tell her that Amanda in the comment
section W Amanda.
Tell her Amanda W please subscribe to
the comment section.
So they're going to come to their
appointment together since they're in
the same
clinic. Unfortunately mine is in
Rosebank so I can't even squeeze myself
in
that's right Someone even said the other
day they blog but you know your friend
can't be on on that I do.
Instagram. No bunnies I'm going to vlog
some now.
>> [laughter]
>> I also dig up my mother got Amanda. I'll
be sneaker. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes.
What's your name?
Rihanna yes, yes, yes.
Get the shoes get the shoes.
Then you can go to Puma Bunny. Oh, I
don't know. I don't know.
Fly.
Fly girls and then face.
Cuz your face is beautiful.
Thanks friend. Same here. What do you
want me to tell you?
Show me anything I vlog I must thank
you.
You magazine lady. What?
I'm joking. I'm joking. I'm joking.
This is our baby. Our baby. Guys, I
watched that baby grow up status.
>> [laughter]
>> Literally and I
always like those pictures and I loved
his updates got Amanda so much.
Beautiful baby by the way. We have fun
and I
And then
She looks like you. She does. She does.
She does done. I saw that baby and knew
that you guys are related.
Amanda went home a few weeks ago, but
she told me tell me I'm feeling about me
on video call and then she show me show
me I almost cried. That was so cute.
That was so cute.
I love that baby so much.
>> Do people look like this?
>> [singing and music]
>> If you're a potential
and you buy the door
>> I can hear that baby is single.
I'm still
Amanda and I came to get something to
eat. I chopped my sister off and now
we're getting something to eat and I'll
talk to you guys tomorrow cuz there's
nothing else to show you. Thank you.
No problem. Thank you.
So she mixed up our order like she got
it wrong twice. I corrected her and she
came back she still got it wrong. I was
like no, passion fruit and lemonade not
lemonade only. Where's the passion
fruit?
So she she started apologizing like yo,
I'm so sorry. I'm still new here. I'm in
training.
Yeah, she's like I'm in training.
Thank you for being so patient with me.
I'm like no, it's okay mama take your
time. So now when she dropped off the
drink, I'm like yes, thank you. She's
like thank you for being so patient with
me. Come on man, like people sometimes
just need grace. Like don't be mean,
brah. They're just service providers.
Like be nice. It doesn't cost you an arm
and a leg to just be nice to someone. So
for her to even point it out like you,
thank you for being so patient with me.
How do you guys treat these people? Like
they're traumatized.
They are traumatized.
>> The emphasis on the trauma.
>> Thank you.
>> I'm thinking that's your first one.
>> My?
>> Your order because you were
>> Yeah.
>> She was the last one.
Guys, this is what I ordered.
I ordered some prawns, rice, fries.
Yes, friend. Amanda on the other end,
nothing because she took too long to
place an order
and the waitress came only 10 minutes
after. So my food has arrived but hers
hasn't. Tumi, you can have some of my
fries.
>> [snorts]
>> You're welcome.
I'll talk to you guys tomorrow. Maybe
when I get home but most probably
tomorrow.
Bye.
Aw, you still do that?
That's cute.
Imagine.
Guys, we spoke too soon. The food is
gone.
The food is gone. It's gone.
It's gone. The manager and the waitress
came to our table.
>> She spoke too soon.
>> We spoke too soon, Yianni.
>> The manager and the waitress came to our
table. They're like, "Hi, sorry. I think
there's been a little bit of an error.
The food that you have is not your food.
It belongs to someone else. They swapped
your order by mistake."
The lady, the one who was saying, "Thank
you for being patient with me, the new
girl.
Wow, [\h__\h] And I had already I had two
fries.
Oh, so many of those are fries.
Tell me, I wanted to have some of those.
If I go up and I say to her, "Sister, I
bought what's going on here?" Because
the manager was just standing at our
table like, "Hi, hello."
What did you tell her?
Yeah, I saw you.
>> [laughter]
>> Imagine the manager says, "Come, you eat
for free. Just post on Instagram."
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, this is your food, friend. Shame.
Okay, right on time. Yeah, we got our
food. Cheers, friends.
Cheers.
Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Can you touch it?
You You listen to what she thought the
manager was going to say.
No, no, no. I think I was thanking you.
>> Thank you.
>> Touch it. Touch it.
>> I thought the manager was going to come
and say,
"Because you guys are beautiful
Instagrammers.
You're not going to pay for your bill."
Here's an Instagram.
>> But Sbu Fikile Nkwanyana
So Masikane
This is our Tatana Ngomso. how I'm
turning home. So, papa in here.
I don't know what you want to do with
your life.
What is that number? Mhm, this is some
nano Amanda look.
Okay, my skin is so
bad.
>> [laughter]
>> I need to do something.
>> Yes.
I need to do something like this.
It's so cool.
I like personalities and stuff.
>> [music]
[music]
[clears throat]
>> Okay.
Properly not the same as
>> [laughter]
>> me. Oh, oh, TD. Say
Okay.
OOTD.
>> [clears throat]
[screaming]
[laughter]
>> I'm done, Ken. Say hi for the camera,
Momma.
Thanks, girl. I'll talk to you later.
Love you.
Hi, y'all. How you guys doing?
I am
ready to go and shoot for Fashion. Oh,
look at what I got. Look, it's so
pretty. It says Princess Street. Wow,
sure. Cuz once again, Alana and Jay,
this is This is my sanctuary. This is my
This is my man cave. Anyways, I'll shoot
those at day nine, so we have to go take
a reel for this outfit. My mom says it's
giving corporate betty. She's so right.
I like it, but I just feel like
I'm not used to seeing myself in like
suits and stuff. I still have to adjust
up
the scarf situation cuz I just folded it
together. But otherwise, the outfit in
its entirety is really beautiful. I'll
probably talk to you guys after because
we are going to a
party. I'll see you
maybe later today when we heading to the
party. So, see you later.
Hi.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Drew my [music] hands
across the solar flares.
And isn't me that you want ME TO
>> GUYS!
GUYS! I MET I MET a pretty lady at this
party. She just told me now that we
share a birthday. That's crazy. Oh,
crazy thing. She's the first person that
I know that I share a birthday with and
she has a twin. SO, NOW THERE'S THREE OF
US.
LOVE YOU, ZAH. What's your name?
>> Hunter.
>> Are you twins?
>> No, I'm her cousin. FROM VEGAS.
>> MYLENE.
MYLENE, BYE-BYE.
>> [laughter]
>> MYLENE, BYE-BYE. It's the next day. I
couldn't speak to you guys
at the party. Someone said I'm always
out of breath. You know what? You're so
right.
>> [laughter]
>> It's because, guys, I slept on the top
floor.
So, I always have to walk like
So, it's the constant up and down these
stairs, Betuna.
Bear with me. But anyways, um there was
nothing much to show you from the party
yesterday because I didn't even stay
that long. I was only here for like I
think an hour tops. I didn't stay more
than
1 hour. Woo!
Good timing.
Woo!
>> [sighs]
>> But anyways, y'all, I did see a lot of
familiar faces. Oh, blackie baby pano
ban bani. See if them and Fargo were
there. I saw a lot more mutuals,
actually. There were a lot of people
there, like a lot. But I didn't stay
because
I low key have social anxiety and I
To be honest, I just wanted to go home.
>> [laughter]
>> I genuinely just wanted to be I
genuinely just wanted to be in my space.
Like I wanted to chill in my house,
switch on the heater, chill in my
pajamas, order food and snacks and watch
TV. Like that's what I wanted to do.
Like I didn't feel like being outside,
so that's why I didn't stay long.
Anyways, um
you guys saw the outfit
I had gone to the mall to look for an
outfit cuz the theme was all black. And
the whole outfit was only worn for 2
minutes
cuz I literally got it just so I could
wear to that um party cuz I didn't have
like something warm that's all black
also. I do have like dresses and stuff,
but I don't have like jackets. So I
found like this that the dress dress
jacket whatever thingamajig from Zara. I
think that was like 1.2-ish.
Somewhere there and then I also got like
perfumes and stuff as well. I got this
gardenia one for my bag cuz I like to
have like small sized perfumes to keep
in my bag just to yeah, smell good
throughout the day. And then I also got
this hypnotic vanilla. If there's one
perfume you're going to get from Zara,
if you're vanilla girly, if you like
like sweet really nice girly scents,
hypnotic vanilla is the girl that she
thinks she is down through and through
and I promise you. But yeah, anyways,
that's it. That was really nice. I'm
wrapping up this vlog. This is the last
scene
um from this week. Today is Saturday, so
I have to start editing so you guys can
get this vlog tomorrow. If you don't get
it tomorrow, then it's going to have to
be Monday. I feel like you guys already
know by now if I'm not done editing and
uploading by Sunday evening, usually I
just push the vlog um to Monday. So you
know, if you don't get it on Sunday,
you're getting it on Monday, but I'm
pushing for tomorrow cuz I know how much
this [\h__\h] means to y'all, man.
Also, I just got back from doing my
nails. I did like something nice and
cute and simple. It's just a cute
Frenchy with
polka dots. You guys remember I broke a
nail, this one. I like it came out like
everything like my natural nail came out
with
the tip. If you're on my finsta, you
know what I'm talking about.
So, I had to wait for it to grow out. I
think it's been a couple of weeks now
and I was lucky starting to feel so out
of my element. Plus, I'm finally over my
ugly little finger and I wanted to post
so I actually went to go do that today
but I got like a very simple design just
to bambisa cuz I feel like this is
literally hanging on hopes and prayers
and I don't know what anytime like
there's literally
no nail bed. I've only grown this much
nail bed. This side is just raw flesh.
So, when I tell you it's hanging on
hopes and prayers, trust me it is. So, I
didn't want to get something too
extravagant or too heavy or long or
whatever just in case and yeah, I'm
lucky also feeling like this cute short
girly vibe for now.
Um,
I've got some KFC. I haven't had KFC in
a while. I've got some KFC for dinner.
Oh, also happy National Girlfriends Day,
y'all. I'm going out with my mates
later. So, I actually want to like put
something in my stomach first cuz I
haven't eaten the whole day. Like I left
the house early to run errands. From
there I was in the nail salon for like
hours. Just got back home. It's I think
it's about 5:00 6:00 p.m. Goku was
supposed to link at like 7:30. So, I
just want to eat quickly because I know
like once we are there people just want
drinks. So,
yeah, this is it for the vlog. Thank you
so much for watching till the end. If
you have not subscribed yet, please make
sure you hit the subscribe button and
the notification bell so you're notified
next time a video drops [bell] on this
channel. I'll see you guys same place,
same time next week. Love you loads.
Bye.